Seyfullah Çapkın

Game Developer & Lecturer

Istanbul · +90 544 864 3999 · sevfullahcapkin@gmail.com

Portfolio

Profile

I've been working in the software field since 2017. I gravitated here because of my interest in the gaming industry and have produced successful projects around the world in this field. I like to follow new technologies and I'm currently trying to improve myself in C++, SQL, .Net and Python.

Work experience

Beykoz University, Lecturer | Istanbul, Turkey

09/2024 - Present

Freelance, Game Developer | Istanbul, Turkey

06/2023 - Present

I provide game development and optimization services to companies or individuals with my knowledge and experience.

Gameflex, Game Developer | Istanbul, Turkey

11/2021 - 02/2023

I worked as a game developer at Gameflex where I worked on developing two hit games and created several other games as well. This role provided a platform for me to polish game development skills. For one of the hit games, I technically resolved optimization issues. I improved my proficiency in using tools such as Firebase, XCode and Android Studio as well as analyzing issues that arise when developing apps for various platforms and devices. Working collaboratively with my team, we ensured that the games were user-friendly in order to enhance the overall gaming experience

Trifles Games, Game Developer | Istanbul, Turkey

06/2021 - 11/2021

I learned how to improve the quality and feel of my games with small details.

Virtual Projects, Game Developer | Istanbul, Turkey

06/2020 - 06/2021

I worked with Virtual Projects company one-on-one for a year. During this time, we received mentoring support and technical training that provided by the Virtual Projects studio. I improvement my skills on game design and game software

ITEE, Information Technology Assistant | USA (Remote)

02/2019 - 06/2020

Supported 150+ Windows, Mac OS, Ubuntu, CentOS, and iOS users in their IT needs, consistently delivering high user satisfaction. Maintained 2 Windows Servers, Active Directory, DNS, and Group Policies, ensuring seamless operation and security adherence. Managed software packages and Apple OS mobile equipment, ensuring a secure user experience. Handled the management of 200+ service and client mailboxes and licenses utilizing Google Workspace.

Achievements: Developed Google Sheet Typescript scripts to integrate asset information across multiple sheets, enabling efficient report generation for audits and increasing efficiency by over %60. Built a custom Flutter mobile app for centralized contact information access, streamlining communication in a company with high employee turnover.

Education

Beykoz University, Digital Game Design

GPA:3.31

2019 - 2023

Karadeniz Technical University, Computer Engineering I dropped out of university in 3rd grade

2012 - 2016

Programming Languages: C# - advanced; HLSL - intermediate; C++ - intermediate; Python - beginner; SQL -

beginner; .Net -beginner- Dart - beginner

Engine: Unity - advanced, Unreal Engine- beginner

Tools: Github - advanced; Sourcetree - advanced; XCode - intermediate; Android Studio - intermediate;

Bitbucket - intermediate; Trello - advanced; Jira - intermediate;

Fields: Gameplay, Tools, Scripting, UI, SDK & Third Party Software Integration

Languages: Turkish - native; English - intermediate